<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Generated by Fujitsu XWand 7.1.0042 -->
<link:linkbase xmlns:link="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/linkbase" xmlns:xbrli="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/instance" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/linkbase http://www.xbrl.org/2003/xbrl-linkbase-2003-12-31.xsd http://www.c-ebs.org/eu/fr/esrs/corep/2005-09-30/ref-corep-2005-09-30 ref-corep-2005-09-30.xsd http://www.xbrl.org/2004/ref ref-2004-08-10.xsd" xmlns:t-md="http://www.c-ebs.org/eu/fr/esrs/corep/2005-12-31/t-md-2005-12-31" xmlns:ref-corep="http://www.c-ebs.org/eu/fr/esrs/corep/2005-09-30/ref-corep-2005-09-30">
  <link:referenceLink xlink:type="extended" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/link">
    <link:loc xlink:type="locator" xlink:href="t-md-2005-12-31.xsd#t-md_BasicInformationDimension" xlink:label="BasicInformationDimension" xlink:title="BasicInformationDimension"/>
    <link:reference xlink:type="resource" xlink:label="reference_BasicInformationDimension" xlink:role="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/role/reference" xlink:title="reference_BasicInformationDimension" id="reference_BasicInformationDimension">
      <ref-corep:Comment>GENERAL COMMENT: This template may be required for each individual model used and/or for the aggregation of all the individual models. Accordingly, in the case of the aggregation of all the individual models, some of the codes that follows, that may be incompatible at the individual level, may be reported simultaneously. </ref-corep:Comment>
      <ref-corep:Comment>Instrument code: "The Instrument code indicates the instrument category or categories covered by the regulatory model: 1 = equities; 2 = debt instruments; 3 = foreign currencies; 4 = commodities. For instance, if a VaR (total) is calculated for equities, debt instruments and foreign currencies, the code is 123." </ref-corep:Comment>
      <ref-corep:Comment>Specific Risk Equities Calculation Code: "Indicates the specific risk calculation code for equities. These code are:  1 = specific risk is not modeled;  2 = specific risk is modeled, including event and default risk (cfannex V, paragraph 9 of directive 93/6/EEC);   3 = specific risk is modeled, excluding event and default risk, with that part of the value-at risk that concerns specific risk (cf. annex V, paragraph 8, a) of the directive 93/6/EEC);  4 = specific risk is modeled, excluding event and default risk, with a calculation for subtrading books involving specific risk (cf. annex V, paragraph 8, b) of directive 93/6/EEC)." </ref-corep:Comment>
      <ref-corep:Comment>Specific risk debt instrument calculation code:"Indicate the specific risk calculation code for debt instruments. These code are:  1 = specific risk is not modeled;  2 = specific risk is modeled, including event and default risk (cfannex V, paragraph 9 of directive 93/6/EEC);   3 = specific risk is modeled, excluding event and default risk, with that part of the value-at risk that concerns specific risk (cf. annex V, paragraph 8, a) of the directive 93/6/EEC);  4 = specific risk is modeled, excluding event and default risk, with a calculation for subtrading books involving specific risk (cf. annex V, paragraph 8, b) of directive 93/6/EEC)." </ref-corep:Comment>
      <ref-corep:Comment>P&amp;L code used for the calculation of number of overshootings: "The P&amp;L code indicates the type of results that are used to calculate the plus-factor (cf. annex V, paragraph 7 of the directive 93/6/EEC):  1 = actual trading results for the days concerned (cf. annex V, paragraph 3 of the directive 93/06/EEC);  2 = hypothetical trading results for the days concerned on the positions fixed at the end of the previous (trading) day (cf. annex V, paragraph 3 of the directive 93/6/EEC"</ref-corep:Comment>
      <ref-corep:Comment>Holding period of internal VaR: Holding period used for risk management purpose (no legal reference); To be filled out in case that the internal VaR calculation is based on a holding period different from 10 days. To be filled out in case that the internal VaR calculation is based on a holding period different from 10 days</ref-corep:Comment>
      <ref-corep:Comment>Confidence interval of internal VaR: Confidence interval used for risk management purpose (no legal reference); To be filled out in case that the internal VaR calculation is based on a confidence interval different from 99 %. To be filled out in case that the internal VaR calculation is based on a confidence interval different from 99 %</ref-corep:Comment>
    </link:reference>
    <link:referenceArc xlink:type="arc" xlink:arcrole="http://www.xbrl.org/2003/arcrole/concept-reference" xlink:from="BasicInformationDimension" xlink:to="reference_BasicInformationDimension" xlink:title="reference: BasicInformationDimension to reference_BasicInformationDimension"/>
  </link:referenceLink>
</link:linkbase>
